Johnroe Paulo Cañamaque

Web Application Developer

Knowledgeable Web Application Developer specializing on developing web applications and performing data engineering activities with superior attention to details. Persistent and result oriented. Always strives to create satisfactory applications with minimal supervision. A leader by example and a flexible team player.

jpcanamaque@gmail.com



Tanza, Cavite



github.com/jpcanamaque

+639178414126



in linkedin.com/in/jpcanamaque



ipcanamaque

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Application Developer

WebSan Inc.

April 2022-present

- Served as lead web application developer for integration projects and intellectual property projects
- Served as technical lead of the company IP team.
- Resource person for in-house technical trainings
- Served as administrator for systems deployment

Trainer (Part-time)

Software Development Academy

January 2022 - present

Taught Python development for local and international students

Programmer

FullScale (Gigabook Inc.)

January 2022 - April 2022

Served as remote resource person for web development projects for company clients

Programmer Analyst II

Analog Devices Inc. (formerly Maxim Integrated)

April 2015 – December 2021

- Developed in-house web applications, visualization, and dashboards for manufacturing and engineering
- Served as Level 3 Support for MSS Team applications
- Provided data ETLs for business analysis
- Served as Administrator for Systems Deployment and IT Governance
- Served as Business Analyst for primarily owned projects
- Resource person for in-house technical trainings
- Employee of the Quarter for Q4 2019 Nominee

Instructor

Cavite State University

June 2013 – April 2015

- Taught IT-related course subjects to college students
- Served as Technical Critic for Undergraduate Thesis

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Computer Science (units)

University of the Philippines – Los Banos January 2018 – January 2019

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Cavite State University - Carmona June 2009 - April 2013

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tools

Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, SVN, Git, npm, pip, doxygen, MS Visual Studio, Office 365, Selenium, Tableau, JIRA, Confluence

Programming Language

PHP (Drupal, Laravel, Codelgniter), JavaScript (VueJS, React, nodejs), Python (Django, Flask), C#, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Flutter

Database Management

MySQL, MariaDB, Oracle 11c, MS SQL

Operating Systems

Microsoft Windows 10, Windows 7, CentOS, RHEL7

Research and Planning

Identifying problems, gathering requirements, developing tests and evaluations, project documentation

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Project Management Flexibility Listening Communication **Problem Solving** Teamwork